<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Salons Death on Take Two</title>
    <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/storylines/salons-death/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Salons Death on Take Two</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/storylines/salons-death/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>July 5, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-5-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-5-2015/</guid>
      <description>Praise God! The Waran team was able to leave Madang as scheduled on Tuesday morning. The flight was early enough that they were able to make it all the way home that same day. Morex and Betty accompanied them so that made for an easier trip for them since they had lots of help right with them.
Each of the team members carried with them fresh copies of Romans and Jude so they could continue reading through them yet again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 14, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-14-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-14-2015/</guid>
      <description>Waran checking is under way! Praise God that the men arrived as expected on Tuesday, the 9th. We were able to check 3 full days and checked Romans 1-5, except for the last 3 verses of chapter 5. This progress is actually ahead of where we need to be to complete the work in the time David Robinson has left to work.
Samuel arrived looking exhausted and unwell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 31, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-31-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-31-2015/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for standing with us this week. It has been a difficult week for the whole Waran team.
Background information to help you understand: Cell phone cover is not available in Yar village, where Samuel lives. They have to hike about 20 minutes to a piece of high ground where the signal gets through. As a result, they can call out when they need to but we can&amp;rsquo;t call in when we need to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update on Prayer for Samuel Sangon &amp; Family</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/update-on-prayer-for-samuel-sangon--family/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/update-on-prayer-for-samuel-sangon--family/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Late this afternoon (Tuesday, May 26, PNG time) I received a call from a Waran man in Wewak town to let me know that they had found the body of Salon very late afternoon on Monday. She was found in the water very near where the children had been playing. Due to the lateness of the time, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t possible for anyone in the village to hike to where they can make a cellphone connection and call us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 24, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-24-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-24-2015/</guid>
      <description>With everything that is in me, I would like to not have to write this message tonight. We may need more than two minutes of your time praying this week.
We are in pain. Today, Sunday, May 24th, the youngest child and only daughter of our co-translator Samuel Sangon went missing. Salon (Sharon) is about three years old. After church she was playing with other children, at least some of the time with a large group of children playing in the river where there is a sandy, sloping shore to the river.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>