<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tok Pisin on Take Two</title>
    <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/languages/tok-pisin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tok Pisin on Take Two</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/languages/tok-pisin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>June 7, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-7-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-7-2015/</guid>
      <description>Samuel and the Waran checking team were not able to come in on the flight on Friday, June 5th, as we had hoped. We didn&amp;rsquo;t have contact with anyone from Yar village until Thursday morning when Samuel called. He wanted to let me know the team was ready to come in for the checking session. I told him of Friday&amp;rsquo;s flight but making that that would have meant he would have had to immediately pack up and head up to the airstrip at Likan and it just wasn&amp;rsquo;t physically possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My word will not return to me empty.</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/my-word-will-not-return-to-me-empty./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/my-word-will-not-return-to-me-empty./</guid>
      <description>The Waran checking team returned home on Tuesday and Morex, Samuel&amp;rsquo;s brother, returned on the flight. He is now in the hospital awaiting surgery, perhaps this week.
Konamby was one of the checking team. He is a pastor who has often been involved in several checking sessions so he has heard much of the Waran New Testament already. He also has copies of most of the books we have completed so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Things Matter</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/little-things-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/little-things-matter/</guid>
      <description>John 19:37 in the NIV reads:
 and, as another scripture says, &amp;ldquo;They will look on the one they have pierced.&amp;rdquo;
 The Waran version translated back into English that had been provided to the consultant read:
 And another talk also remains like this, They will remain seeing the man who was penetrated by means of a spear.
 That is what he expected to hear from the checker when he orally translated from Waran into the Tok Pisin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 19, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/april-19-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/april-19-2015/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes you just have to scratch your head!
John 10:40 in the NIV version says, &amp;ldquo;Then Jesus went back across the Jordan to the place where John had been baptizing in the early days. There he stayed.&amp;rdquo;
When Samuel read aloud the Waran version of that verse and one of the checkers gave a translation into the Tok Pisin language, the consultant thought he heard something odd. He asked the checkers, &amp;ldquo;Who was baptizing?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>