<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Consultant Checking John on Take Two</title>
    <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/storylines/consultant-checking-john/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Consultant Checking John on Take Two</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/storylines/consultant-checking-john/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My word will not return to me empty.</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/my-word-will-not-return-to-me-empty./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/my-word-will-not-return-to-me-empty./</guid>
      <description>The Waran checking team returned home on Tuesday and Morex, Samuel&amp;rsquo;s brother, returned on the flight. He is now in the hospital awaiting surgery, perhaps this week.
Konamby was one of the checking team. He is a pastor who has often been involved in several checking sessions so he has heard much of the Waran New Testament already. He also has copies of most of the books we have completed so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Things Matter</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/little-things-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/little-things-matter/</guid>
      <description>John 19:37 in the NIV reads:
 and, as another scripture says, &amp;ldquo;They will look on the one they have pierced.&amp;rdquo;
 The Waran version translated back into English that had been provided to the consultant read:
 And another talk also remains like this, They will remain seeing the man who was penetrated by means of a spear.
 That is what he expected to hear from the checker when he orally translated from Waran into the Tok Pisin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 12, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/april-12-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/april-12-2015/</guid>
      <description>The Waran translation team arrived as expected on Wednesday and the consultant checking of John&amp;rsquo;s Gospel got underway on Thursday. By Friday afternoon we have completed checking 1:1-4:42. In order for the consultant to complete the work within the days he has available, we need to check about 80 verses a day. So far we are almost on target.
Once the consultant session ends for the day, then the Waran team goes over any verses where problems have surfaced and revises them to make sure the meaning is correct.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>