<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Furlough 2015 on Take Two</title>
    <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/storylines/furlough-2015/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Furlough 2015 on Take Two</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/storylines/furlough-2015/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>January 17, 2016</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/01/january-17-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/01/january-17-2016/</guid>
      <description>The past few months have flown by. We have had the privilege to see some of you and hope to see more of you in the near future. We have been able to spend some very special times with family. God is good!
When William and Samuel last worked together before our furlough, they saw how close they were to finishing the Advisor Check of the Waran New Testament. Neither wanted to wait to finish that until we returned from furlough, primarily because they saw that the rest of 2016 would go better if that stage were already finished when we returned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/12/merry-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/12/merry-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Near the end of her life, one of my grandparents&amp;rsquo; neighbors told this story:
One day my grandpa came walking down the old railroad track that ran along the edge of his farm, just whistling away. This wasn&amp;rsquo;t unusual but the neighbor thought his whistle that morning sounded different, and went out to see why. When grandpa came to the corner, she asked, &amp;ldquo;Bill, why the happy tune?&amp;rdquo; He replied with a big smile, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m going to have a grandson (me)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 6, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/09/september-6-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/09/september-6-2015/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your prayers this past week. Robin&amp;rsquo;s tests went well. The tests confirmed that eating gluten-free is helping her. The doctor has recommended that she continue with a restricted diet and treatment regimen. While it would have been nice to be able to eat freely again, Robin expected this is how it would end up. She is committed to continuing on with the special diet.
Take Two Prayer Points:  Thank God that the restricted diet Robin has been following has resulted in improvements to her gastro-intestinal health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 30, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-30-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-30-2015/</guid>
      <description>By the time we realized on Tuesday that we had allowed last Sunday to pass without sending out a Take Two, our time was in extremely short supply. Our departure was at hand and our list of tasks to do didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be getting any shorter. I continued to believe that I was going to finish my list right up until Bethaney pulled up to our door at 5:45 on Friday morning to take us to the airport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 16, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-16-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-16-2015/</guid>
      <description>The last couple of weeks we have reported on events from the heights. There will be none of that this week. We are back to the mundane, the all-to-frequent chore of sorting and packing up. With less than two weeks to go before we leave PNG for furlough, it simply must get done now. I have often said that the thing most likely to cause me to stop being a missionary is the packing and moving.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>