<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Likan on Take Two</title>
    <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/places/likan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Likan on Take Two</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/places/likan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>September 4, 2016</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/09/september-4-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/09/september-4-2016/</guid>
      <description>The Waran team arrived in Madang on Monday morning as expected. However, there was a little drama involved. At 7:15 I received a call from Likan, where the airstrip is, saying that the men had not gotten there on Sunday evening as expected. The plane had left Madang already but had 2-3 stops before it was to land in Likan. There were some nervous moments for me until around 8 o&amp;rsquo;clock when another call told me they had made it to Likan and the plane was not yet there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 9, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-9-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-9-2015/</guid>
      <description>After the convention, we all returned to Likan. I had originally thought that I might ride to Yar village, Samuel&amp;rsquo;s village, with some of the Yar people who attended the convention so that we could start a village check of the book of James. In a village check we read the Scripture to groups of people. We ask questions and find out from them if they are getting the right meaning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 26, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-26-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-26-2015/</guid>
      <description>William, Bethaney and interns left Likan and traveled by river to Yar Friday July 24th. They are to do village checking of the book of James during their time there.
Early Monday morning they will travel on downriver to Angoram, where the road meets the river. From there they will go overland by public transportation to Wewak and catch a commercial flight back to Madang. William will be staying in Wewak for a couple of extra days in hopes to talk to government officials concerning the airstrip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 19, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-19-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-19-2015/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday July 14th was a typical plane day. Rush, rush, rush. We were expecting two planes to get everyone where they needed to be. I became the designated driver to free up Bethaney to do other things before the second plane which she was to be on. William and I loaded up the cargo and two other passengers and headed for the airport. The plane was waiting on us when we got there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 12, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-12-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-12-2015/</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday, Lord willing, Bethaney and I will fly to Likan, accompanied by Breanna, Max, and Chris, the three summer interns, and Michelle, their coach. On Thursday, the 16th, the church convention will begin in Klorowom village, another Waran village not far from Likan, and go through Sunday. Since this is in the heart of Waran territory, I expect most of the attendees to be Waran people. However, there will be several other languages with sizable contingents as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Returning to Full-time Translation</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/returning-to-full-time-translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/returning-to-full-time-translation/</guid>
      <description>God has provided new co-workers to take on the role William has been filling in the PBTPNG Finance Office for the past four years. Even though not much time has been spent on Translation during this time in Finance, God has helped William and Samuel to make some progress. We are starting a new phase &amp;ndash; as of February 2015 our full attention has returned to the Waran Translation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>