<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Konamby on Take Two</title>
    <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/people/konamby/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Konamby on Take Two</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/people/konamby/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>August 9, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-9-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-9-2015/</guid>
      <description>After the convention, we all returned to Likan. I had originally thought that I might ride to Yar village, Samuel&amp;rsquo;s village, with some of the Yar people who attended the convention so that we could start a village check of the book of James. In a village check we read the Scripture to groups of people. We ask questions and find out from them if they are getting the right meaning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 5, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-5-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-5-2015/</guid>
      <description>Praise God! The Waran team was able to leave Madang as scheduled on Tuesday morning. The flight was early enough that they were able to make it all the way home that same day. Morex and Betty accompanied them so that made for an easier trip for them since they had lots of help right with them.
Each of the team members carried with them fresh copies of Romans and Jude so they could continue reading through them yet again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 14, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-14-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-14-2015/</guid>
      <description>Waran checking is under way! Praise God that the men arrived as expected on Tuesday, the 9th. We were able to check 3 full days and checked Romans 1-5, except for the last 3 verses of chapter 5. This progress is actually ahead of where we need to be to complete the work in the time David Robinson has left to work.
Samuel arrived looking exhausted and unwell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My word will not return to me empty.</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/my-word-will-not-return-to-me-empty./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/my-word-will-not-return-to-me-empty./</guid>
      <description>The Waran checking team returned home on Tuesday and Morex, Samuel&amp;rsquo;s brother, returned on the flight. He is now in the hospital awaiting surgery, perhaps this week.
Konamby was one of the checking team. He is a pastor who has often been involved in several checking sessions so he has heard much of the Waran New Testament already. He also has copies of most of the books we have completed so far.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>