<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2015 Interns on Take Two</title>
    <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/storylines/2015-interns/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2015 Interns on Take Two</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/storylines/2015-interns/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>August 2, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-2-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-2-2015/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your prayers for our time out among the Waran people.
The convention went very awesomely well. The majority of the attendees were Waran, but large contingents from the Kianying Balang language area on the Biwat River and the La&amp;rsquo;o language area on the upper Keram River, as well as a few from other areas added to the crowd. While the official count showed 1734 people in attendance, I know some people arrived after the count was taken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 26, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-26-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-26-2015/</guid>
      <description>William, Bethaney and interns left Likan and traveled by river to Yar Friday July 24th. They are to do village checking of the book of James during their time there.
Early Monday morning they will travel on downriver to Angoram, where the road meets the river. From there they will go overland by public transportation to Wewak and catch a commercial flight back to Madang. William will be staying in Wewak for a couple of extra days in hopes to talk to government officials concerning the airstrip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 19, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-19-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-19-2015/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday July 14th was a typical plane day. Rush, rush, rush. We were expecting two planes to get everyone where they needed to be. I became the designated driver to free up Bethaney to do other things before the second plane which she was to be on. William and I loaded up the cargo and two other passengers and headed for the airport. The plane was waiting on us when we got there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 12, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-12-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-12-2015/</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday, Lord willing, Bethaney and I will fly to Likan, accompanied by Breanna, Max, and Chris, the three summer interns, and Michelle, their coach. On Thursday, the 16th, the church convention will begin in Klorowom village, another Waran village not far from Likan, and go through Sunday. Since this is in the heart of Waran territory, I expect most of the attendees to be Waran people. However, there will be several other languages with sizable contingents as well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>