<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Take Two</title>
    <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Take Two</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>September 4, 2016</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/09/september-4-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/09/september-4-2016/</guid>
      <description>The Waran team arrived in Madang on Monday morning as expected. However, there was a little drama involved. At 7:15 I received a call from Likan, where the airstrip is, saying that the men had not gotten there on Sunday evening as expected. The plane had left Madang already but had 2-3 stops before it was to land in Likan. There were some nervous moments for me until around 8 o&amp;rsquo;clock when another call told me they had made it to Likan and the plane was not yet there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 28, 2016</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/08/august-28-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/08/august-28-2016/</guid>
      <description>Another busy week is finally over. No big adventures; just a lot of daily grind. It seemed to just keep going and going! But, in the end, it is all good.
The back-translation of James is complete. Praise the Lord for that.
We have heard from Samuel. He and 4 others were to travel upriver to Likan village today. A Missionary Aviation Fellowship plane will be going tomorrow morning to pick them up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 17, 2016</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/01/january-17-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/01/january-17-2016/</guid>
      <description>The past few months have flown by. We have had the privilege to see some of you and hope to see more of you in the near future. We have been able to spend some very special times with family. God is good!
When William and Samuel last worked together before our furlough, they saw how close they were to finishing the Advisor Check of the Waran New Testament. Neither wanted to wait to finish that until we returned from furlough, primarily because they saw that the rest of 2016 would go better if that stage were already finished when we returned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/12/merry-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/12/merry-christmas/</guid>
      <description>Near the end of her life, one of my grandparents&amp;rsquo; neighbors told this story:
One day my grandpa came walking down the old railroad track that ran along the edge of his farm, just whistling away. This wasn&amp;rsquo;t unusual but the neighbor thought his whistle that morning sounded different, and went out to see why. When grandpa came to the corner, she asked, &amp;ldquo;Bill, why the happy tune?&amp;rdquo; He replied with a big smile, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m going to have a grandson (me)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 6, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/09/september-6-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/09/september-6-2015/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your prayers this past week. Robin&amp;rsquo;s tests went well. The tests confirmed that eating gluten-free is helping her. The doctor has recommended that she continue with a restricted diet and treatment regimen. While it would have been nice to be able to eat freely again, Robin expected this is how it would end up. She is committed to continuing on with the special diet.
Take Two Prayer Points:  Thank God that the restricted diet Robin has been following has resulted in improvements to her gastro-intestinal health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 30, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-30-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-30-2015/</guid>
      <description>By the time we realized on Tuesday that we had allowed last Sunday to pass without sending out a Take Two, our time was in extremely short supply. Our departure was at hand and our list of tasks to do didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be getting any shorter. I continued to believe that I was going to finish my list right up until Bethaney pulled up to our door at 5:45 on Friday morning to take us to the airport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 16, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-16-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-16-2015/</guid>
      <description>The last couple of weeks we have reported on events from the heights. There will be none of that this week. We are back to the mundane, the all-to-frequent chore of sorting and packing up. With less than two weeks to go before we leave PNG for furlough, it simply must get done now. I have often said that the thing most likely to cause me to stop being a missionary is the packing and moving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 9, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-9-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-9-2015/</guid>
      <description>After the convention, we all returned to Likan. I had originally thought that I might ride to Yar village, Samuel&amp;rsquo;s village, with some of the Yar people who attended the convention so that we could start a village check of the book of James. In a village check we read the Scripture to groups of people. We ask questions and find out from them if they are getting the right meaning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 2, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-2-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-2-2015/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your prayers for our time out among the Waran people.
The convention went very awesomely well. The majority of the attendees were Waran, but large contingents from the Kianying Balang language area on the Biwat River and the La&amp;rsquo;o language area on the upper Keram River, as well as a few from other areas added to the crowd. While the official count showed 1734 people in attendance, I know some people arrived after the count was taken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 26, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-26-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-26-2015/</guid>
      <description>William, Bethaney and interns left Likan and traveled by river to Yar Friday July 24th. They are to do village checking of the book of James during their time there.
Early Monday morning they will travel on downriver to Angoram, where the road meets the river. From there they will go overland by public transportation to Wewak and catch a commercial flight back to Madang. William will be staying in Wewak for a couple of extra days in hopes to talk to government officials concerning the airstrip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 19, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-19-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-19-2015/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday July 14th was a typical plane day. Rush, rush, rush. We were expecting two planes to get everyone where they needed to be. I became the designated driver to free up Bethaney to do other things before the second plane which she was to be on. William and I loaded up the cargo and two other passengers and headed for the airport. The plane was waiting on us when we got there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 12, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-12-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-12-2015/</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday, Lord willing, Bethaney and I will fly to Likan, accompanied by Breanna, Max, and Chris, the three summer interns, and Michelle, their coach. On Thursday, the 16th, the church convention will begin in Klorowom village, another Waran village not far from Likan, and go through Sunday. Since this is in the heart of Waran territory, I expect most of the attendees to be Waran people. However, there will be several other languages with sizable contingents as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 5, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-5-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-5-2015/</guid>
      <description>Praise God! The Waran team was able to leave Madang as scheduled on Tuesday morning. The flight was early enough that they were able to make it all the way home that same day. Morex and Betty accompanied them so that made for an easier trip for them since they had lots of help right with them.
Each of the team members carried with them fresh copies of Romans and Jude so they could continue reading through them yet again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 28, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-28-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-28-2015/</guid>
      <description>Praise God! We finished the checking of Romans and Jude on Tuesday. Jude went much better than expected so we didn&amp;rsquo;t need the time that the consultant had available on Wednesday. The Waran team began Wednesday to go through the book and make correction at places that the consultant recommended changes or refinements be made. We had done all the easy corrections as we went through during the checking session, but some needed more concentrated thought to resolve and were set aside for later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 21, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-21-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-21-2015/</guid>
      <description>The Waran team has had a fruitful week. We steadily moved through the verses of Romans, to arrive at 14:19 where we will start checking again on Monday morning. Lord willing, we will be able to complete Romans on Tuesday. Seeing that we were progressing well, our consultant has prepared to check Jude when we finish Romans. Considering our late start, this is an unexpected bonus.
Another praise item this week: Morex has been declared healed and technically released from the hospital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 14, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-14-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-14-2015/</guid>
      <description>Waran checking is under way! Praise God that the men arrived as expected on Tuesday, the 9th. We were able to check 3 full days and checked Romans 1-5, except for the last 3 verses of chapter 5. This progress is actually ahead of where we need to be to complete the work in the time David Robinson has left to work.
Samuel arrived looking exhausted and unwell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 7, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-7-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-7-2015/</guid>
      <description>Samuel and the Waran checking team were not able to come in on the flight on Friday, June 5th, as we had hoped. We didn&amp;rsquo;t have contact with anyone from Yar village until Thursday morning when Samuel called. He wanted to let me know the team was ready to come in for the checking session. I told him of Friday&amp;rsquo;s flight but making that that would have meant he would have had to immediately pack up and head up to the airstrip at Likan and it just wasn&amp;rsquo;t physically possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 31, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-31-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-31-2015/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for standing with us this week. It has been a difficult week for the whole Waran team.
Background information to help you understand: Cell phone cover is not available in Yar village, where Samuel lives. They have to hike about 20 minutes to a piece of high ground where the signal gets through. As a result, they can call out when they need to but we can&amp;rsquo;t call in when we need to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update on Prayer for Samuel Sangon &amp; Family</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/update-on-prayer-for-samuel-sangon--family/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/update-on-prayer-for-samuel-sangon--family/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Late this afternoon (Tuesday, May 26, PNG time) I received a call from a Waran man in Wewak town to let me know that they had found the body of Salon very late afternoon on Monday. She was found in the water very near where the children had been playing. Due to the lateness of the time, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t possible for anyone in the village to hike to where they can make a cellphone connection and call us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 24, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-24-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-24-2015/</guid>
      <description>With everything that is in me, I would like to not have to write this message tonight. We may need more than two minutes of your time praying this week.
We are in pain. Today, Sunday, May 24th, the youngest child and only daughter of our co-translator Samuel Sangon went missing. Salon (Sharon) is about three years old. After church she was playing with other children, at least some of the time with a large group of children playing in the river where there is a sandy, sloping shore to the river.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 17, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-17-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-17-2015/</guid>
      <description>Please take two minutes daily and pray for these items.
 Praise God that Morex was able to have surgery on Thursday. Everything seemed to go well during the surgery, but today there was a setback when some of the stitches turned loose. Pray that repair will be quickly made on Monday and the healing process will proceed without further incident.
 Pray that Samuel will be able to complete his house before he needs to return to Madang with a team of checkers for the consultant check of Romans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 10, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-10-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-10-2015/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for taking two minutes out of your busy day to pray for us and the Waran Translation.
Update from last week regarding the tractor: The dealer is unwilling to give a quote for a new tractor. There are currently none in country and they do not yet have prices for those that are on their way. Until we are able to get an actual quotation from the dealer, the process is stalled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My word will not return to me empty.</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/my-word-will-not-return-to-me-empty./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/my-word-will-not-return-to-me-empty./</guid>
      <description>The Waran checking team returned home on Tuesday and Morex, Samuel&amp;rsquo;s brother, returned on the flight. He is now in the hospital awaiting surgery, perhaps this week.
Konamby was one of the checking team. He is a pastor who has often been involved in several checking sessions so he has heard much of the Waran New Testament already. He also has copies of most of the books we have completed so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Things Matter</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/little-things-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/little-things-matter/</guid>
      <description>John 19:37 in the NIV reads:
 and, as another scripture says, &amp;ldquo;They will look on the one they have pierced.&amp;rdquo;
 The Waran version translated back into English that had been provided to the consultant read:
 And another talk also remains like this, They will remain seeing the man who was penetrated by means of a spear.
 That is what he expected to hear from the checker when he orally translated from Waran into the Tok Pisin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 19, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/april-19-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/april-19-2015/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes you just have to scratch your head!
John 10:40 in the NIV version says, &amp;ldquo;Then Jesus went back across the Jordan to the place where John had been baptizing in the early days. There he stayed.&amp;rdquo;
When Samuel read aloud the Waran version of that verse and one of the checkers gave a translation into the Tok Pisin language, the consultant thought he heard something odd. He asked the checkers, &amp;ldquo;Who was baptizing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 12, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/april-12-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/april-12-2015/</guid>
      <description>The Waran translation team arrived as expected on Wednesday and the consultant checking of John&amp;rsquo;s Gospel got underway on Thursday. By Friday afternoon we have completed checking 1:1-4:42. In order for the consultant to complete the work within the days he has available, we need to check about 80 verses a day. So far we are almost on target.
Once the consultant session ends for the day, then the Waran team goes over any verses where problems have surfaced and revises them to make sure the meaning is correct.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He is Risen!</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/he-is-risen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/he-is-risen/</guid>
      <description>The Sabbath day finished and on Sunday the sun wanted to come up. And Mary, the woman from Makdala village, and another Mary both went, wanting to see the corpse village. They did that and one of the Big (One)&amp;rsquo;s messengers left heaven and came down. He did that and that mother earthquake [a large quake] immediately happened. It did that and he went to the stone that was hiding the corpse hole door and rolled it away and put it to the side and sat on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Returning to Full-time Translation</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/returning-to-full-time-translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/returning-to-full-time-translation/</guid>
      <description>God has provided new co-workers to take on the role William has been filling in the PBTPNG Finance Office for the past four years. Even though not much time has been spent on Translation during this time in Finance, God has helped William and Samuel to make some progress. We are starting a new phase &amp;ndash; as of February 2015 our full attention has returned to the Waran Translation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>