<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Consultant Checking Romans on Take Two</title>
    <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/storylines/consultant-checking-romans/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Consultant Checking Romans on Take Two</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/storylines/consultant-checking-romans/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>July 5, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-5-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-5-2015/</guid>
      <description>Praise God! The Waran team was able to leave Madang as scheduled on Tuesday morning. The flight was early enough that they were able to make it all the way home that same day. Morex and Betty accompanied them so that made for an easier trip for them since they had lots of help right with them.
Each of the team members carried with them fresh copies of Romans and Jude so they could continue reading through them yet again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 28, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-28-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-28-2015/</guid>
      <description>Praise God! We finished the checking of Romans and Jude on Tuesday. Jude went much better than expected so we didn&amp;rsquo;t need the time that the consultant had available on Wednesday. The Waran team began Wednesday to go through the book and make correction at places that the consultant recommended changes or refinements be made. We had done all the easy corrections as we went through during the checking session, but some needed more concentrated thought to resolve and were set aside for later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 21, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-21-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-21-2015/</guid>
      <description>The Waran team has had a fruitful week. We steadily moved through the verses of Romans, to arrive at 14:19 where we will start checking again on Monday morning. Lord willing, we will be able to complete Romans on Tuesday. Seeing that we were progressing well, our consultant has prepared to check Jude when we finish Romans. Considering our late start, this is an unexpected bonus.
Another praise item this week: Morex has been declared healed and technically released from the hospital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 14, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-14-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-14-2015/</guid>
      <description>Waran checking is under way! Praise God that the men arrived as expected on Tuesday, the 9th. We were able to check 3 full days and checked Romans 1-5, except for the last 3 verses of chapter 5. This progress is actually ahead of where we need to be to complete the work in the time David Robinson has left to work.
Samuel arrived looking exhausted and unwell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 7, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-7-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-7-2015/</guid>
      <description>Samuel and the Waran checking team were not able to come in on the flight on Friday, June 5th, as we had hoped. We didn&amp;rsquo;t have contact with anyone from Yar village until Thursday morning when Samuel called. He wanted to let me know the team was ready to come in for the checking session. I told him of Friday&amp;rsquo;s flight but making that that would have meant he would have had to immediately pack up and head up to the airstrip at Likan and it just wasn&amp;rsquo;t physically possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 31, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-31-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-31-2015/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for standing with us this week. It has been a difficult week for the whole Waran team.
Background information to help you understand: Cell phone cover is not available in Yar village, where Samuel lives. They have to hike about 20 minutes to a piece of high ground where the signal gets through. As a result, they can call out when they need to but we can&amp;rsquo;t call in when we need to.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>