<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Likan Airstrip Maintenance on Take Two</title>
    <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/storylines/likan-airstrip-maintenance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Likan Airstrip Maintenance on Take Two</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/storylines/likan-airstrip-maintenance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>May 10, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-10-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-10-2015/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for taking two minutes out of your busy day to pray for us and the Waran Translation.
Update from last week regarding the tractor: The dealer is unwilling to give a quote for a new tractor. There are currently none in country and they do not yet have prices for those that are on their way. Until we are able to get an actual quotation from the dealer, the process is stalled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My word will not return to me empty.</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/my-word-will-not-return-to-me-empty./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/my-word-will-not-return-to-me-empty./</guid>
      <description>The Waran checking team returned home on Tuesday and Morex, Samuel&amp;rsquo;s brother, returned on the flight. He is now in the hospital awaiting surgery, perhaps this week.
Konamby was one of the checking team. He is a pastor who has often been involved in several checking sessions so he has heard much of the Waran New Testament already. He also has copies of most of the books we have completed so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Returning to Full-time Translation</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/returning-to-full-time-translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/returning-to-full-time-translation/</guid>
      <description>God has provided new co-workers to take on the role William has been filling in the PBTPNG Finance Office for the past four years. Even though not much time has been spent on Translation during this time in Finance, God has helped William and Samuel to make some progress. We are starting a new phase &amp;ndash; as of February 2015 our full attention has returned to the Waran Translation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>