<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>William Butler on Take Two</title>
    <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/people/william-butler/</link>
    <description>Recent content in William Butler on Take Two</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/people/william-butler/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>January 17, 2016</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/01/january-17-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/01/january-17-2016/</guid>
      <description>The past few months have flown by. We have had the privilege to see some of you and hope to see more of you in the near future. We have been able to spend some very special times with family. God is good!
When William and Samuel last worked together before our furlough, they saw how close they were to finishing the Advisor Check of the Waran New Testament. Neither wanted to wait to finish that until we returned from furlough, primarily because they saw that the rest of 2016 would go better if that stage were already finished when we returned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 30, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-30-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-30-2015/</guid>
      <description>By the time we realized on Tuesday that we had allowed last Sunday to pass without sending out a Take Two, our time was in extremely short supply. Our departure was at hand and our list of tasks to do didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be getting any shorter. I continued to believe that I was going to finish my list right up until Bethaney pulled up to our door at 5:45 on Friday morning to take us to the airport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 16, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-16-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-16-2015/</guid>
      <description>The last couple of weeks we have reported on events from the heights. There will be none of that this week. We are back to the mundane, the all-to-frequent chore of sorting and packing up. With less than two weeks to go before we leave PNG for furlough, it simply must get done now. I have often said that the thing most likely to cause me to stop being a missionary is the packing and moving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 9, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-9-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-9-2015/</guid>
      <description>After the convention, we all returned to Likan. I had originally thought that I might ride to Yar village, Samuel&amp;rsquo;s village, with some of the Yar people who attended the convention so that we could start a village check of the book of James. In a village check we read the Scripture to groups of people. We ask questions and find out from them if they are getting the right meaning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 2, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-2-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-2-2015/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your prayers for our time out among the Waran people.
The convention went very awesomely well. The majority of the attendees were Waran, but large contingents from the Kianying Balang language area on the Biwat River and the La&amp;rsquo;o language area on the upper Keram River, as well as a few from other areas added to the crowd. While the official count showed 1734 people in attendance, I know some people arrived after the count was taken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 26, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-26-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-26-2015/</guid>
      <description>William, Bethaney and interns left Likan and traveled by river to Yar Friday July 24th. They are to do village checking of the book of James during their time there.
Early Monday morning they will travel on downriver to Angoram, where the road meets the river. From there they will go overland by public transportation to Wewak and catch a commercial flight back to Madang. William will be staying in Wewak for a couple of extra days in hopes to talk to government officials concerning the airstrip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 19, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-19-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-19-2015/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday July 14th was a typical plane day. Rush, rush, rush. We were expecting two planes to get everyone where they needed to be. I became the designated driver to free up Bethaney to do other things before the second plane which she was to be on. William and I loaded up the cargo and two other passengers and headed for the airport. The plane was waiting on us when we got there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 10, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-10-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-10-2015/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for taking two minutes out of your busy day to pray for us and the Waran Translation.
Update from last week regarding the tractor: The dealer is unwilling to give a quote for a new tractor. There are currently none in country and they do not yet have prices for those that are on their way. Until we are able to get an actual quotation from the dealer, the process is stalled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My word will not return to me empty.</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/my-word-will-not-return-to-me-empty./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/my-word-will-not-return-to-me-empty./</guid>
      <description>The Waran checking team returned home on Tuesday and Morex, Samuel&amp;rsquo;s brother, returned on the flight. He is now in the hospital awaiting surgery, perhaps this week.
Konamby was one of the checking team. He is a pastor who has often been involved in several checking sessions so he has heard much of the Waran New Testament already. He also has copies of most of the books we have completed so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Things Matter</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/little-things-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/little-things-matter/</guid>
      <description>John 19:37 in the NIV reads:
 and, as another scripture says, &amp;ldquo;They will look on the one they have pierced.&amp;rdquo;
 The Waran version translated back into English that had been provided to the consultant read:
 And another talk also remains like this, They will remain seeing the man who was penetrated by means of a spear.
 That is what he expected to hear from the checker when he orally translated from Waran into the Tok Pisin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 19, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/april-19-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/april-19-2015/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes you just have to scratch your head!
John 10:40 in the NIV version says, &amp;ldquo;Then Jesus went back across the Jordan to the place where John had been baptizing in the early days. There he stayed.&amp;rdquo;
When Samuel read aloud the Waran version of that verse and one of the checkers gave a translation into the Tok Pisin language, the consultant thought he heard something odd. He asked the checkers, &amp;ldquo;Who was baptizing?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>