<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Samuel Sangon on Take Two</title>
    <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/people/samuel-sangon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Samuel Sangon on Take Two</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/people/samuel-sangon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>September 4, 2016</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/09/september-4-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/09/september-4-2016/</guid>
      <description>The Waran team arrived in Madang on Monday morning as expected. However, there was a little drama involved. At 7:15 I received a call from Likan, where the airstrip is, saying that the men had not gotten there on Sunday evening as expected. The plane had left Madang already but had 2-3 stops before it was to land in Likan. There were some nervous moments for me until around 8 o&amp;rsquo;clock when another call told me they had made it to Likan and the plane was not yet there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 28, 2016</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/08/august-28-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/08/august-28-2016/</guid>
      <description>Another busy week is finally over. No big adventures; just a lot of daily grind. It seemed to just keep going and going! But, in the end, it is all good.
The back-translation of James is complete. Praise the Lord for that.
We have heard from Samuel. He and 4 others were to travel upriver to Likan village today. A Missionary Aviation Fellowship plane will be going tomorrow morning to pick them up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 17, 2016</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/01/january-17-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2016/01/january-17-2016/</guid>
      <description>The past few months have flown by. We have had the privilege to see some of you and hope to see more of you in the near future. We have been able to spend some very special times with family. God is good!
When William and Samuel last worked together before our furlough, they saw how close they were to finishing the Advisor Check of the Waran New Testament. Neither wanted to wait to finish that until we returned from furlough, primarily because they saw that the rest of 2016 would go better if that stage were already finished when we returned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 9, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-9-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-9-2015/</guid>
      <description>After the convention, we all returned to Likan. I had originally thought that I might ride to Yar village, Samuel&amp;rsquo;s village, with some of the Yar people who attended the convention so that we could start a village check of the book of James. In a village check we read the Scripture to groups of people. We ask questions and find out from them if they are getting the right meaning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 28, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-28-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-28-2015/</guid>
      <description>Praise God! We finished the checking of Romans and Jude on Tuesday. Jude went much better than expected so we didn&amp;rsquo;t need the time that the consultant had available on Wednesday. The Waran team began Wednesday to go through the book and make correction at places that the consultant recommended changes or refinements be made. We had done all the easy corrections as we went through during the checking session, but some needed more concentrated thought to resolve and were set aside for later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 21, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-21-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-21-2015/</guid>
      <description>The Waran team has had a fruitful week. We steadily moved through the verses of Romans, to arrive at 14:19 where we will start checking again on Monday morning. Lord willing, we will be able to complete Romans on Tuesday. Seeing that we were progressing well, our consultant has prepared to check Jude when we finish Romans. Considering our late start, this is an unexpected bonus.
Another praise item this week: Morex has been declared healed and technically released from the hospital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 14, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-14-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-14-2015/</guid>
      <description>Waran checking is under way! Praise God that the men arrived as expected on Tuesday, the 9th. We were able to check 3 full days and checked Romans 1-5, except for the last 3 verses of chapter 5. This progress is actually ahead of where we need to be to complete the work in the time David Robinson has left to work.
Samuel arrived looking exhausted and unwell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 7, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-7-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/06/june-7-2015/</guid>
      <description>Samuel and the Waran checking team were not able to come in on the flight on Friday, June 5th, as we had hoped. We didn&amp;rsquo;t have contact with anyone from Yar village until Thursday morning when Samuel called. He wanted to let me know the team was ready to come in for the checking session. I told him of Friday&amp;rsquo;s flight but making that that would have meant he would have had to immediately pack up and head up to the airstrip at Likan and it just wasn&amp;rsquo;t physically possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 31, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-31-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-31-2015/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for standing with us this week. It has been a difficult week for the whole Waran team.
Background information to help you understand: Cell phone cover is not available in Yar village, where Samuel lives. They have to hike about 20 minutes to a piece of high ground where the signal gets through. As a result, they can call out when they need to but we can&amp;rsquo;t call in when we need to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update on Prayer for Samuel Sangon &amp; Family</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/update-on-prayer-for-samuel-sangon--family/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/update-on-prayer-for-samuel-sangon--family/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Late this afternoon (Tuesday, May 26, PNG time) I received a call from a Waran man in Wewak town to let me know that they had found the body of Salon very late afternoon on Monday. She was found in the water very near where the children had been playing. Due to the lateness of the time, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t possible for anyone in the village to hike to where they can make a cellphone connection and call us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 24, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-24-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-24-2015/</guid>
      <description>With everything that is in me, I would like to not have to write this message tonight. We may need more than two minutes of your time praying this week.
We are in pain. Today, Sunday, May 24th, the youngest child and only daughter of our co-translator Samuel Sangon went missing. Salon (Sharon) is about three years old. After church she was playing with other children, at least some of the time with a large group of children playing in the river where there is a sandy, sloping shore to the river.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 17, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-17-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/may-17-2015/</guid>
      <description>Please take two minutes daily and pray for these items.
 Praise God that Morex was able to have surgery on Thursday. Everything seemed to go well during the surgery, but today there was a setback when some of the stitches turned loose. Pray that repair will be quickly made on Monday and the healing process will proceed without further incident.
 Pray that Samuel will be able to complete his house before he needs to return to Madang with a team of checkers for the consultant check of Romans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My word will not return to me empty.</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/my-word-will-not-return-to-me-empty./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/05/my-word-will-not-return-to-me-empty./</guid>
      <description>The Waran checking team returned home on Tuesday and Morex, Samuel&amp;rsquo;s brother, returned on the flight. He is now in the hospital awaiting surgery, perhaps this week.
Konamby was one of the checking team. He is a pastor who has often been involved in several checking sessions so he has heard much of the Waran New Testament already. He also has copies of most of the books we have completed so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Things Matter</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/little-things-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/little-things-matter/</guid>
      <description>John 19:37 in the NIV reads:
 and, as another scripture says, &amp;ldquo;They will look on the one they have pierced.&amp;rdquo;
 The Waran version translated back into English that had been provided to the consultant read:
 And another talk also remains like this, They will remain seeing the man who was penetrated by means of a spear.
 That is what he expected to hear from the checker when he orally translated from Waran into the Tok Pisin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 19, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/april-19-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/04/april-19-2015/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes you just have to scratch your head!
John 10:40 in the NIV version says, &amp;ldquo;Then Jesus went back across the Jordan to the place where John had been baptizing in the early days. There he stayed.&amp;rdquo;
When Samuel read aloud the Waran version of that verse and one of the checkers gave a translation into the Tok Pisin language, the consultant thought he heard something odd. He asked the checkers, &amp;ldquo;Who was baptizing?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>