<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yar on Take Two</title>
    <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/places/yar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Yar on Take Two</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/places/yar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>August 9, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-9-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/08/august-9-2015/</guid>
      <description>After the convention, we all returned to Likan. I had originally thought that I might ride to Yar village, Samuel&amp;rsquo;s village, with some of the Yar people who attended the convention so that we could start a village check of the book of James. In a village check we read the Scripture to groups of people. We ask questions and find out from them if they are getting the right meaning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 26, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-26-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-26-2015/</guid>
      <description>William, Bethaney and interns left Likan and traveled by river to Yar Friday July 24th. They are to do village checking of the book of James during their time there.
Early Monday morning they will travel on downriver to Angoram, where the road meets the river. From there they will go overland by public transportation to Wewak and catch a commercial flight back to Madang. William will be staying in Wewak for a couple of extra days in hopes to talk to government officials concerning the airstrip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 12, 2015</title>
      <link>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-12-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://taketwo.tylerbutler.com/2015/07/july-12-2015/</guid>
      <description>On Tuesday, Lord willing, Bethaney and I will fly to Likan, accompanied by Breanna, Max, and Chris, the three summer interns, and Michelle, their coach. On Thursday, the 16th, the church convention will begin in Klorowom village, another Waran village not far from Likan, and go through Sunday. Since this is in the heart of Waran territory, I expect most of the attendees to be Waran people. However, there will be several other languages with sizable contingents as well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>